<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="catledgeHereticLoreSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<root>
    <charLore sourceLog="The Heretic">A blue flash appeared in one of the storage bays of the
        Contact Light. The chaos ensuing on the ship was a perfect distraction. As soon as <char
            name="Heretic">Kur-skan</char> stepped out the portal she ducked into a sprint. She had
        no time. She weaved between gunfire and fireballs, between blasts of Vagrant energy and
        on-board security systems. They paid no mind to the feathered figure as she darted through
        closing blast doors. She flew quickly down the halls of the ship. Despite it being her first
        time onboard a human vessel, she could sense the electromagnets in the walls – and where
        they all joined. She corked right, shooting into the ventilation shafts with a bang. The
        captain barely had a chance to see her before she blasted sideways out into the control
        room. She tore out two windblades as he reached for his pistol. The captain fell to the
        ground in intervals. Her momentum crashed her into the control panels, both feet digging
        deep into monitors. She didn’t need those. Nimble, clawed fingers began ripping across
        keypads. She quickly split and rewired components, reaching into her feathered pouches for
        more bridges and other electronics. Various capacitors fell onto the floor. This ship was
        big, but not complex – and more importantly, it could still fly. But she had to go fast, or
        he – And before she could finish her thought, he appeared in a flash of thunder. Blue and
        green light reflected off of his sword, cascading around the bridge. A cape fluttered, and
        Providence landed lightly on his feet. <char name="Heretic">Kur-skan</char> bent her head
        backwards over her body, hands still tearing at panels. He was much faster than she
        expected. But maybe he would – Her last thoughts were interrupted instantly by a crystalline
        blade.</charLore>
    <itmLore>
        <log sourceLog="Visions of Heresy">…and for her betrayal, and her lies, and her scheming
            ways, the Heretic was violently separated into four distinctive pieces, each to be
            scattered across the farthest depths of the Moon. First, her many eyes were plucked from
            her skull and sealed in boiling glass, forced to gaze upon her failure...” -<part n="3"
                >The Evisceration of Kur-skan the Heretic, III</part></log>


        <log sourceLog="Hooks of Heresy">“…her arms were warped into terrible blades, so she may no
            longer find joy in study or tooling…” -<part n="4">The Evisceration of Kur-skan the
                Heretic, IV</part></log>


        <log sourceLog="Strides of heresy">“Her legs were scattered to the two poles of the moon,
            twisted in a wicked position, in a field of obsidian thorns…" -<part n="5">The
                Evisceration of Kur-skan the Heretic, V</part></log>


        <log sourceLog="Essence of Heresy">“…and her heart, too wicked and full of hate, was left
            where she once stood – at the site of her betrayal.” -<part n="6">The Evisceration of
                Kur-skan the Heretic, VI</part></log>
    </itmLore>
</root>
